Guide to the Seymour Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Thomas Day Seymour, 1850-1909; Series VII; 7'6" (18 boxes)
  - Personal and Miscellaneous
    - Receipts, 1897, undated (Box 31, Folder 302)
    - Last will and testament
      See: box 104, folder 20
    - Memorials, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 302a)
      See also: box 104, folder 21
    - Miscellaneous, 1864-1907, undated (Box 31, Folder 303-305)
- Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour, 1866-(1886-1907)-1914; Series VIII; 1'8" (4 boxes)
  Sarah Melissa (Hitchcock) Seymour was born September 27, 1846, in Columbus, Ohio. She was the daughter of Rev. Henry Lawrence Hitchcock, president of Western Reserve College, and Clarissa Mary Sophia (Ford) Hitchcock. A graduate of Lake Erie Seminary, "Sadie" married Thomas Day Seymour, then a young classics professor at Western Reserve College, on July 2, 1874. In Hudson, Ohio, Sadie gave birth to their two daughters, Elizabeth (known as Beth) Day (1876) and Clara Hitchcock (1880).
  Not long after Clara's birth, the family moved to New Haven, Connecticut. In 1885 a son, Charles, was born. In 1891 the family was joined by Thomas' parents, but this domestic arrangement was short lived; in December Nathan Perkins Seymour contracted influenza and died. Sadie continued to care for her mother-in-law until Elizabeth's death in 1900.
  A short time after the death of her mother-in-law, Sadie embarked on a long trip to Ohio and Indiana to visit family and friends and her alma mater. Freed from family obligations Sadie learned to love traveling. In 1901 Sadie accompanied Thomas to England, Switzerland, and Scotland, where he represented Yale at the 450th anniversary of Glasgow University. Heartened by this experience, Thomas and Sadie made plans for an extended stay in Europe. In January, Sadie and Clara sailed for Europe and spent many weeks traveling through Italy, Austria, Switzerland, and France. Joined by Thomas two months later, the family remained in Europe through August. The entire family was reunited in England for a visit with Charles.
  The next five years brought happy changes in the family with Charles close by as a student in Yale College and Clara's marriage in 1906. 1907 though proved to be a year of illness and tragedy. In February Sadie and her sister-in-law, Sarah Parsons, set out to visit Clara in Florida. They arrived to find that Clara was showing the first symptoms of what proved to be typhoid fever. Sadie brought Clara back to New Haven to recover, but during the summer Charles, too, was stricken with typhoid. Just before Thanksgiving Thomas fell ill with pneumonia, grew steadily worse, and died on the last day of the year.
  Sadie continued to live quietly with Beth. They moved to a smaller house and spent some time abroad. When Beth married English sculptor John Angel, Sadie accompanied her to London for the wedding and then lived with the couple. She shared with them the problems of wartime life and the birth, on March 21, 1915, of their son. One year and one day later, Sadie died.
  Correspondence contains letters addressed to Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour alone or in conjunction with her children, and from Mrs. Seymour to non-family members. In both sub-sections the material is arranged alphabetically by sender, and chronologically within each folder.
  Of particular interest are the letters Sadie wrote for the round robin newsletter with classmates. Each year when the round robin arrived, Sadie would remove the letter she had written the previous year and would substitute a new one. Fortunately, she kept many of these letters, which chronicle family events and travels, and her own interests, activities, and reading. Also of note are letters from daughters Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel and Clara (Seymour) St. John concerning their experiences at Bryn Mawr College. There are in addition many letters from husband Thomas relaying to Sadie the happenings in New Haven and at Yale while she was absent traveling.
  Writings is composed of one folder containing an account by Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour of her husband's final illness.
  Printed Material consists of one folder of clippings from British and American newspapers.
  Personal and Memorabilia contains one folder of receipts and another of invitations.
  Hitchcock Family Papers consists of six folders of correspondence of members of the Hitchcock family and one folder of printed material. The material is arranged alphabetically by the names of family members.
  - Correspondence
    - Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour from
      - A-D, 1883-1910, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - E-K, [1883]-1908 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - L-S, 1893-[1915?], undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - T-Z, unidentified, 1875-1908, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1889-1914, undated (Box 32, Folder 5-8)
      - Clapp, Edward B., 1908 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Dean, Katharine (Parsons), 1880 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Hitchcock, Charles, 1883 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Hitchcock, Clara M., 1891-1900, undated (Box 32, Folder 12-13)
      - Hitchcock, Herbert, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Hitchcock, Grace, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Parsons, Harriet Day, 1889 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Parsons, Sarah (Seymour), 1883-1890, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - St. John, Clara (Seymour), 1889-1908, undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - St. John, George, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Seymour, Charles (1843-1913), 1906-1911, undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1892-1911, undated (Box 33, Folder 21-22)
      - Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1879-1892, undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins), 1911 (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - Seymour, Nathan Perkins, undated (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1866-1886 (Box 33, Folder 26-29)
      - Seymour, Thomas Day, [1886-1898?] (Box 34, Folder 30-39)
      - Seymour, Thomas Day, [1900-1907?], undated fragments (Box 35, Folder 40-46)
    - Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour to
      - Classmates, 1893-1912 (Box 35, Folder 47-48)
      - "James", undated (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Writings
    - Account of final illness of Thomas Day Seymour, 1907 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Printed Material
    - Clippings from British and American newspapers, Circa 1914 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Personal and Memorabilia
    - Receipts, 1886, 1899, undated (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Children's wedding announcements, 1911, 1914 (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - Poetry and music, miscellaneous, 1908-1917, undated (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Hitchcock Family Papers
    - Correspondence
      - Clara M. Hitchcock from Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), undated (Box 35, Folder 55)
      - Clara M. Hitchcock to Mrs. Cutler, 1868 (Box 35, Folder 56)
      - Clara M. Hitchcock to unidentified, undated (Box 35, Folder 57)
      - Henry L. Hitchcock to Cutter, Professor, 1867-1868 (Box 35, Folder 58)
      - Peter Hitchcock to Cook, [E?], 1820 (Box 35, Folder 59)
      - Nabby (Cook) Hitchcock to Cook, Abigail, 1813 (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - Writings
      - Henry L. Hitchcock, Abraham Lincoln: A Sermon, 1865 (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - Printed Material
      - In Memoriam: Henry L. Hitchcock, [1873?] (Box 35, Folder 62)
- Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel, 1880-(1896-1905)-1937; Series IX; 1'2.5" (4 boxes)
  Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel, Thomas Day and Sarah Hitchcock Seymour's first child, was born in the Hudson, Ohio, home of the grandmother for whom she was named. From an early age Elizabeth, known as Beth, exhibited great intelligence and enthusiam for learning.
  In 1893 she graduated from Hillhouse High School in New Haven, Connecticut, and passed the entrance examinations for Yale. While there was no possibility that she might enter the all-male university, it was necessary for her to pass the examination for Yale or Harvard in order to be accepted at Bryn Mawr College. Beth, like her father, loved classics and at Bryn Mawr she majored in Greek. When she graduated in June 1897 she received both the Bachelor of Arts and Master of Arts degrees.
  Following graduation, Beth lived at home with her parents and studied at the Yale Art School. During the summer of 1900 she and Clara accompanied their uncle Charles Seymour to Europe. From 1901 until 1903 Beth taught Greek at Lake Erie College in Painesville, Ohio, the school her mother attended. When poor health forced her to give up teaching permanently, she returned home to live with her parents.
  In 1912 Beth went abroad alone. While she was in Greece she met the promising English sculptor John Angel. Two years later, on April 25, 1914, they were married in London. On March 21, 1915, she gave birth to a son, John Lawrence Angel. A second son, Henry Seymour Angel, was born in 1919.
  In 1925 Beth and her family moved to the United States, where John was commissioned to do a great deal of work for the St. John the Divine Cathedral in New York City. More American work followed, most notably the six bronze doors of St. Patrick's Cathedral in New York. After living for a while in New York City, the family moved to Sandy Hook, Connecticut. This remained their home until Beth's death on January 6, 1942. John stayed on there until his own death eighteen years later.
  Correspondence consists of letters addressed to Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel, which are arranged alphabetically by sender. Substantial letters from Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour convey impressions of daily life in New Haven's academic community.
  Personal and Memorabilia consists of quotations collected by Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel, clippings about John Angel, and miscellaneous material such as invitations and Bryn Mawr College forms. There is also a small painting of a woman, possibly Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel, which may have been painted by John Angel.
  - Correspondence
    - Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel from
      - A-Z, unidentified, fragments, 1883-1908, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Hitchcock, Clara M., 1886-1902 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Lansbury, Clara, [1894-1895?] (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Miller, Rebecca, 1895 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Parsons, Harriet Day, 1887, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Parsons, Sarah Day, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1893-1908, 1919 (Box 36, Folder 7-15)
      - Seymour, Charles (1843-1913), 1888-1892 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963, 1892-1903, 1924 (Box 36, Folder 17-18)
      - Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1880-1886, undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Seymour, Nathan Perkins, 1880-1891 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), [1891-1908?], undated (Box 37, Folder 21-32)
      - Seymour, Thomas Day, [1886-1893?] (Box 37, Folder 33)
      - Seymour, Thomas Day, [1894-1905?], undated (Box 38, Folder 34-45)
  - Personal and Memorabilia
    - Collected quotations, 1899, 1932, undated (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Painting [by John Angel?], undated (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - News clipping about John Angel, 1921 (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous, 1891-1914, undated (Box 39, Folder 49)
- St. John Family, 1886-1964; Series X; 7.5" (2 boxes)
  Clara Hitchcock (Seymour) St. John was born March 28, 1880, in her grandfather's home in Hudson, Ohio. She attended New Haven's public schools, entered Bryn Mawr at the age of sixteen, and graduated summa cum laude in 1900. That summer her uncle Charles Seymour took Clara and her sister to Europe for three months. Upon her return, Clara undertook the running of her parents' household to relieve her mother. During this period she assisted her father in the preparation of his books, Plato, Apology and Crito and Life in the Homeric Age; she also published an anthology of her own, Masterpieces of Greek Literature, in 1902. In 1903, she traveled several months with her family in England and on the Continent.
  On June 23, 1906, Clara married George Clair St, John, a Harvard graduate then teaching English at the Adirondack-Florida School. As its name implies, this school spent part of the year in the Adirondacks and then transported students and faculty alike to Coconut Grove, Florida, for the winter. In the first months of her marriage, Clara gamely accompanied George on this trek. The harrowing experience of Clara's bout with typhoid fever persuaded George to secure employment less removed from civilization, and he accepted a position with the Hackley School. In 1908 he was appointed headmaster of the Choate School, a position he held until his retirement.
  Clara and George had four children: Elizabeth Seymour (1908), George Clair, Jr. (1910), Seymour (1912), and Francis Cushman (1916). Clara's talent for mothering extended beyond her own family to include the boys at Choate. For half a century, both St. Johns exerted a profound influence upon hundreds of outstanding young men who went on to positions of power and success.
  Correspondence contains letters addressed to Clara Hitchcock (Seymour) St. John and George Clair St. John, arranged alphabetically by sender and chronologically within each folder. The section contains many letters from Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel describing married life and child rearing in Britain during World War I.
  Writings consists of a small volume of poetry by Elizabeth Seymour St. John and unpublished poems by Clara St. John.
  Printed Material consists of memorials to Clara St. John and Francis Cushman St. John, obituaries of George St. John, and one folder of miscellaneous printed material.
  - Correspondence
    - Clara Hitchcock (Seymour) St. John from
      - A-Z, [1894?]-[1937] (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1892-1918, undated (Box 40, Folder 2-8)
      - Angel, John, 1915-1916 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - [Hitchcock?], Clara, 1887 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1892-1909, 1917, 1924, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins), [1924?] (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), 1889-1915, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1886-1900, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - "Nita", [1891?] (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Clara Hitchcock (Seymour) St. John to unidentified, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - George Clair St. John from Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1924, 1956-1958 (Box 40, Folder 17-19)
  - Writings
    - Book of poems by Elizabeth Seymour St. John, undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Poetry by Clara Hitchcock (Seymour) St. John, undated (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Printed Material
    - Memorial for Clara Hitchcock (Seymour) St. John, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Memorial for Francis Cushman St. John, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Obituaries, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous, 1900, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Charles Seymour (1885-1963), 1889-1963; Series XI; 7'8" (19 boxes)
  Charles Seymour (1885-1963) was born in New Haven on January 1, 1885. After graduating from Hillhouse High School in 1901, he spent the next three years studying at King's College, Cambridge University and traveling throughout Great Britain and the Continent. He then returned to this country and entered Yale, which awarded him a second bachelor of arts degree in 1904. Immediately taking up his graduate work in history, Charles studied at the University of Freiburg, the Sorbonne, Cambridge University, and Yale, which awarded him the doctorate in history in 1911.
  On May 4 of that year he married Gladys Marion Watkins of Scranton, Pennsylvania, who was the sister of his Yale classmate, Charles Law Watkins. After a honeymoon in Europe, Charles Seymour began his teaching career at Yale.
  As World War I drew to a close, he joined the Inquiry, the group of "experts" recruited by Colonel Edward M. House to prepare for the expected peace conference. He was then selected to attend the conference in Paris and was appointed chief of the Austro-Hungarian Division.
  In the following years Charles Seymour returned to his teaching and writing. He edited The Intimate Papers of Colonel House, spent a year as an exchange professor in Belgium in 1924, and became curator of the House papers, which the Colonel had donated to the Yale University Library.
  In 1927 Charles Seymour was appointed provost of the university, and in 1937 he succeeded James Rowland Angell as president of Yale, a post he held until 1950.
  He devoted his retirement years to overseeing the administration of the House Collection, writing, and traveling. He died August 11, 1963.
  This series contains Charles Seymour's personal and family papers. For the papers he accumulated in his capacity as president of Yale University see: YRG 2A15; for the material relating to his career as an historian and curator of the House Collection see: MSS Group 441.
  Series XI consists of the following sections.
  Correspondence is divided into Correspondence to Charles Seymour and Correspondence from Charles Seymour to others. The material is arranged alphabetically by correspondent, and chronologically within each folder. The section includes many interesting letters from Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel describing her travels and her daily routine in England during World War I. There is also a long series of letters from George St. John from Choate including one in 1960 containing his special insights about Choate graduate John F. Kennedy. Daughter Elizabeth Atwater Seymour also wrote frequently, and her letters provide accounts of life in Washington, the Federal Arts Project, the housing problems during World War II, and her experiences in O.S.S. Later letters, after she had returned to New Haven, contain descriptions of social and political happenings from the point of view of a Stevenson Democrat in a Republican family.
  Writings is a relatively short section since the great majority of Charles Seymour's writings is contained in the record and manuscript groups mentioned above. There are two sub-sections. 1. Writings by Charles Seymour consists of his recollections of his childhood and youth, some poems and essays, a copy of his inaugural address, an article about an ancestor, and memorials for George Townsend and Clive Day. This material is arranged chronologically. 2. Writings by others contains recollections by several relatives of life in Hudson, Ohio, and humorous poems in honor of Charles Seymour.
  Printed Material contains clippings, programs, membership lists, miscellaneous publications, and obituaries of Charles Seymour, and is arranged by category of material.
  Personal and Memorabilia is arranged chronologically.
  Financial Records is arranged alphabetically by category of material.
  - Correspondence
    - Charles Seymour from
      - A-D, 1906-1951, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - E-L, 1910-1960, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - M-R, 1910-1963, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - S-T, 1910-1952 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - U-Z, 1910-1960, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Acheson, Dean, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1889-1918 (Box 42, Folder 7-14)
      - Angel, James Rowland, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - Angel, John, 1916-1954 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - Beves, Donald H., 1931 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Bowers, A. Margaret, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - Bowles, John, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Bradford, Arthur, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - Campbell, Mary, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - Cambridge University, 1911 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - Chamsaur, Gwyn, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - Class of 1908, Yale University, undated (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - Connecticut, State of, Tax Department, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - Davison, F. Trubee, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 26)
      - Day, Katharine Seymour, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - Day, Nancy, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 28)
      - Doolittle, Laura (Seymour), 1951 (Box 43, Folder 29)
      - [Dreir?], Katherine, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 30)
      - Edmondson, Marie, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 31)
      - Eliot, T.S., undated (Box 43, Folder 32)
      - Farnham, Thomas, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 33)
      - Gaillard, Edward, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 34)
      - [Hadley?, Arthur T.], 1915 (Box 43, Folder 35)
      - Halifax, Lord, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 36)
      - Hemingway, Minerva Hart, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 37)
      - Holden, Reuben A., 1962 (Box 43, Folder 38)
      - [Holley, Sarah Day?], [1921?] (Box 43, Folder 39)
      - Howard, James M., Jr., 1944-1959 (Box 43, Folder 40)
      - Howard, James M., III, 1954-1962 (Box 43, Folder 41-42)
      - Howard, Sarah (Seymour), 1928-1945 (Box 43, Folder 43-43a)
      - Hutchinson, Ralph Cooper, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 44)
      - Jones, Louise Seymour, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 45)
      - Law, Ellen Atwater, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 46)
      - Lawton, Carolyn Fox, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 47)
      - Leffingwell, R.C., 1950 (Box 43, Folder 48)
      - McCook, Anson T., 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 49)
      - Morrell, Norman, 1913 (Box 43, Folder 50)
      - Naval War College, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 51)
      - Nettleton, George, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 52)
      - New Haven, City of, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 53)
      - Oxford and Cambridge Dinner, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 54)
      - Parsons, Sarah (Seymour), [1913?] (Box 43, Folder 55)
      - Parsons, Seymour, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 56)
      - Parsons, William E., 1934 (Box 43, Folder 57)
      - [Perrin?], Lester, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 58)
      - Phillips, Duncan, [1937?] (Box 43, Folder 59)
      - Reeve, C. McC., 1942-1944 (Box 43, Folder 60)
      - Roper, Dorothy, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 61)
      - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1890-1945 (Box 43, Folder 62-69)
      - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1947-1958, undated (Box 44, Folder 70-75)
      - St. John, Connie, 1951, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 76)
      - St. John, George, 1935-1960 (Box 44, Folder 77-87)
      - St. John, George, 1961-1962 (Box 45, Folder 88-89)
      - St. John, George C., Jr., 1961 (Box 45, Folder 90)
      - St. John, Seymour, 1948, 1958-1960 (Box 45, Folder 91)
      - Scott, Walter, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 92)
      - [Scranton, Worthington?], 1918-1925 (Box 45, Folder 93)
      - Seymour, Charles (1843-1913), 1909, 1912 (Box 45, Folder 94)
      - Seymour, Charles, Jr., 1918-1950 (Box 45, Folder 95-107)
      - Seymour, Charles, Jr., 1951-1961, undated (Box 46, Folder 108-110)
      - Seymour, Charles, III, 1956-1962 (Box 46, Folder 111)
      - Seymour, Charlotte, 1948-1962 (Box 46, Folder 112-113)
      - Seymour, Charlotte (Ball), 1940-1962 (Box 46, Folder 114-117)
      - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater, 1919-1940 (Box 46, Folder 118-127)
      - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater, 1941-1956 (Box 47, Folder 128-142)
      - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater, 1957-1962, undated (Box 48, Folder 143-150)
      - Seymour, Fannie E., 1940, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 151)
      - Seymour, George Dudley, 1926, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 152)
      - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins), 1908-1910, undated (Box 48, Folder 153-157)
      - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins), 1910-1915 (Box 49, Folder 158-171)
      - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins), 1916-1948, undated (Box 50, Folder 172-183)
      - Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), 1899-1911 (Box 50, Folder 184-188)
      - Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), 1913-1916, undated (Box 51, Folder 189-190)
      - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1896-1907, undated (Box 51, Folder 191-194)
      - Sheppard, J.T., 1950 (Box 51, Folder 195)
      - Stanley, Harold, 1937, 1953-1959 (Box 51, Folder 196)
      - Stimson, Henry, 1936 (Box 51, Folder 197)
      - Tinker, Chauncey B., 1932-1949 (Box 51, Folder 198)
      - Townsend, George, 1935 (Box 51, Folder 199)
      - Tuttle, H. Emerson, 1933-1941 (Box 51, Folder 200)
      - Tweedsmuir, Lord, 1938-1939 (Box 51, Folder 201)
      - Warren, Charles, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 202)
      - Watkins, Charles Law, [1910?] (Box 51, Folder 203)
      - Watkins, Elizabeth (Law), 1911-1919 (Box 51, Folder 204)